Chapter 12.
The next planet was inhabited by a tippler.
This was a very short visit, but it plunged a little prince into deep dejection.
"What are you doing there?"
he said to the tippler, whom he found settled down in silence before a
collection of empty bottles and also a collection of fall bottles.
"I am drinking reply to the tipler with a lugubrious hair Why are you drinking?"
demanded the little prince.
"So that I may forget," replied the tippler.
"Forget what?"
inquired the little prince, who already was sorry for him.
"Forget that I am ashamed," the tipler confessed, hanging his head.
"Ashamed of what?" insisted the little prince, who wanted to help him.
"Ashamed of drinking!"
The tiplo brought his speech to an end, and shut himself up in an impregnable silence.
And the little prince went away, puzzled
grown-ups are certainly very, very odd," he said to himself, as he continued on his journey